{
    "subject": "Eleanor_of_Castile",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Edward_I_of_England",
    "human_readable": "Eleanor of Castile is married to Edward I of England.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8984095454216003,
            "question": "Who was Eleanor of Castile married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8610517382621765,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Eleanor of Castile and Edward I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8179956674575806,
            "question": "To which king was Eleanor of Castile married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7673450112342834,
            "question": "Who reigned as King of England during Eleanor of Castile's marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7623528838157654,
            "question": "Name the wife of Edward I of England."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6864965558052063,
            "question": "What is the name of Eleanor of Castile's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6773942112922668,
            "question": "Was Eleanor of Castile married to a King?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5984256267547607,
            "question": "Which prominent historical figure is known to be married to Edward I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3145940601825714,
            "question": "Who was the Queen Consort during the reign of Edward I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2794340252876282,
            "question": "Who held the title of Queen Consort during the reign of Edward I?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eleanor of Castile is married to Edward I of England.",
            "html": "yago_29899_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the Queen Consort during the reign of Edward I?",
            "html": "yago_29899_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which prominent historical figure is known to be married to Edward I?",
            "html": "yago_29899_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Eleanor of Castile married to a King?",
            "html": "yago_29899_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29899_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29899_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29899_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29899_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29899_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29899_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29899_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29899_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29899_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29899_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer in a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents confirm that Eleanor of Castile was indeed the first wife of King Edward I of England, and that their marriage was a political deal to affirm English sovereignty over Gascony."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Eleanor of Castile was the first wife of King Edward I of England, which directly supports the statement that she was married to Edward I of England."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}